yalantis.com 2019-12-25

# Yalantis Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains what information is collected by Yalantis when you visit the yalantis.com website (hereinafter “the website”), visit any related websites (hereinafter “subdomains”), use any other services provided by Yalantis, or communicate with us by any means including by email, phone, messenger, or any other medium. This Privacy Policy also explains how you can control the information we collect, how this information will be used, and how to contact us. This document describes how we protect your personal data.

  1. ## Who collects data about you

Your data is collected by Yalantis and is not used by or shared with anyone not mentioned in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, comments, or requests related to data collection or this policy, please contact us at [privacy@yalantis.com](mailto:privacy@yalantis.com).

  2. ## What data we collect about you

    1. ### When you contact us

We collect data that you submit through the contact form on our website or that you disclose to us by other means such as orally (over a call) or in writing (in an email or other text message). We collect your full name, email address, phone number, and any additional information you provide.

    2. ### When you subscribe to our updates

When you subscribe to our updates via the blog, we collect the email address you provide and your subscription preferences.

    3. ### When you apply for a job

When you apply to join our team, we collect information from your CV and any additional information you provide us by any written or oral means.

    4. ### Data that is automatically collected when you visit the website and subdomains

      1. #### Third-party services

Our website and subdomains use third-party services to collect standard internet log information and details about visitors’ behavior patterns. To collect this information, we use Google Analytics, Pipedrive, and Crazy Egg. We do this to improve your experience on our website and to provide you with the most relevant information. Google Analytics gives us information about user behavior such as platforms and browsers used to access the website and subdomains, pages visited on the website and subdomains, the region from which a visitor is accessing the website and subdomains, how a visitor accessed our website and subdomains (e.g. via search engines, referring pages, direct visits), and other behavioral information.

This information is processed strictly anonymously. You can find more detailed information about how Google uses information from sites or apps that use its services here: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>. Pipedrive gives us information about referring pages of those who have filled out the contact form on the website, including the path of these users on the website. You can find more detailed information about Pipedrive GDPR compliance here: <https://support.pipedrive.com/hc/en-us/articles/360000335129-Pipedrive-and-GDPR>. Crazy Egg provides us with data on user behavior on our website pages. This information is displayed as heatmaps showing us the most frequently read and clicked parts of each page and is tracked safely and anonymously. You can find more info about data usage and protection here: <https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy>

We carefully investigate all third-party services that we use to make sure they are compliant with all current regulations.

      2. #### Cookies

We use cookies to personalize our service and to improve the experience on our website and subdomains. Here is a list of cookies thaty we use:

Provider| Cookie| Expiration| Description  
---|---|---|---  
Yalantis| _gid| 1 day| Randomly generates a short user ID. Google Analytics uses this cookie to distinguish between users. You can read the full Google Analytics privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. None of your personal data is transferred to Google.  
Yalantis| _r_visits| 〜 1 month| We take care of management and ensure effortless communication so that you our clients can con-centrate on business development.  
Yalantis| _trail_referrer_v2_yalantis-web_session| 20 years1 session| These cookies are used to track which website pages a user has viewed and which articles they have reacted to. They’re used to understand what services a user might be interested in. They also let us understand how exactly users navigate our website to help us improve the website and the services we provide.  
Yalantis| _ym_uid| 〜 1 year| Yandex Metrica cookie for randomly generating a user id. Used for web analytics. O personal data is shared with Yandex.  
Yalantis| devicePixelRatioinnerWidth| 1 session| These cookies track device pixel ratio and inner width. This data is used to determine if a device has a Retina display in order to provide a better UI. More details can be found here: <https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Window/devicePixelRatio><https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Window/innerWidth>  
Yalantis| _gat| 1 day| This cookie does not store any user information. It’s used only to limit the number of requests that have to be made to doubleclick.net.  
YalantisGoogle Analytics| _ga| 2 years| This cookie helps Google Analytics identify visitor sessions.  
Google| 1P_JAR| 1 month| This cookie is used to collect website statistics and track conversion rates.  
Google| AID| 〜 1.5 year| This cookie is used to link your activity across devices if you’ve previously signed in to your Google Account on another device.  
Google| APISIDNID| 〜 2 years6 months| This cookie is used by Google to store user preferences and information for Google Maps.  
Google| DVHSIDSIDCC| 〜 2 years| These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use the website. We use this information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. These cookies collect information anonymously. You can read the full Google Analytics privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.  
Google| SSIDUULE| 2 years| These cookies are used by Google to store user preferences and information for Google and Google Analytics.  
Google| OTZSAPISIDSID| 30 days2 years〜 2 years| These cookies are used for tracking Google analytics and G+ button use.  
DoubleClick by Google| DSIDIDE__gfp_64bcto_lwid| 1 session〜 18 months2 years〜 1 year| DoubleClick is a Google tool for marketing and ads. It uses a set of cookies to collect information and report website usage statistics without personally identifying individual visitors to Google. You can find more detailed information about the tool here: <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types>  
  3. ## How we use your personal data

    1. ### For contacting you

We will use your email address, phone number, or other contact information you provide us by written or oral means for contacting you and providing you with the services and information that you request; it also allows us to correctly respond to your comments and questions.

    2. ### For establishing business relations

If you are an existing customer of Yalantis or we reasonably believe that you might want to be our customer, we will use your email address, phone number, and other contact information you provide us by written or oral means for establishing a business relationship, sending you information about our services, and providing you with updates that may be related to your personal and professional interests.

    3. ### For providing you with information

If you have subscribed to our updates, we will use the email address you provided to send information about our services, recent updates, latest products, case studies, and research.

    4. ### For automated processing

If you visit the website, data about your behavior on the site will be automatically processed by cookies and third-party services to help us better understand your preferences and improve your experience on the website.

  4. ## Third parties

To ensure the security of your sensitive information, we carefully select third-party services that we use. We use exceptional services that claim they are compliant with GDPR and other data protection regulations. You can contact us at [privacy@yalantis.com](mailto:privacy@yalantis.com) for more information about taking appropriate and suitable security measures.

    1. ### Third-party services

Your data may be transferred to third-party services including Google Analytics, Pipedrive, Doscify, Crazy Egg, and SendinBlue all of which are compliant with GDPR and other regulations. Their privacy policies can be found here:  
Google Analytics – <https://policies.google.com/privacy>  
Pipedrive – <https://www.pipedrive.com/en/privacy>  
Docsify – [https://docsify.net/privacy-policy](https://docsify.net/privacy-policy/)  
Crazy Egg – [https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy](https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy/)  
SendinBlue – [https://www.sendinblue.com/legal/privacypolicy](https://www.sendinblue.com/legal/privacypolicy/)

    2. ### Subcontractors

Your data may also be transferred to subcontractors. During this process, data may be transferred to parties located in countries outside the EU that are not bound by EU data protection regulations (for example, to parties in Ukraine). However, to protect your data, we always sign contracts with our subcontractors that contain provisions for the protection of user data.

  5. ## How to withdraw your consent for collecting, processing, and using your data

You have the right to withdraw consent for collecting, processing, and using your data at any time by sending an email to [privacy@yalantis.com](mailto:privacy@yalantis.com). If you are receiving our emails, you can unsubscribe by clicking the Unsubscribe button in any email or by just replying with a request to unsubscribe.

  6. ## How long your data is stored for

Your data will be stored until the moment you withdraw your consent or our business relationship is broken off, whichever happens later.

  7. ## Your rights as a data subject

    1. ### Right to access

You have the right to find out what data is being collected and processed, how it is being used, for how long it is being stored, if your data has been transferred to any third parties, and how you can withdraw your consent for data collection, processing, and use.

    2. ### Right to rectification

You have the right to ask that we rectify inaccurate personal data. Taking into account the purposes of data processing, you have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.

    3. ### Right to erasure

You have the right to obtain from us the erasure of your personal data when this personal data is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed, when you withdraw your consent on which the processing was based, or when your data is processed illegally.

    4. ### Right to restrict processing

You have the right to restrict us from processing your data if:  
\- you contest the accuracy of your personal data; in this case, we shall not process your data for a period sufficient for us to verify the accuracy of the personal data;  
\- the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your personal data and request the restriction of its use instead;  
\- your personal data is no longer needed for the purposes of processing but is still required by you for the establishment, exercise, or defence of legal claims;  
\- you object to processing your personal data on grounds related to your particular situation; in this case, we only have the right to process your personal data if we provide legitimate grounds for processing it that are more compelling than your grounds for not processing.

  8. ## How you can raise a complaint

You can raise a complaint be sending an email to [privacy@yalantis.com](mailto:privacy@yalantis.com).

  9. ## Privacy Policy updates

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Updates may be in response to changes to existing law or changes to security standards and best practices for third-party services or tools that we use. We will update this Privacy Policy as we consider it necessary. 

We use cookies to personalize our service and to improve your experience on the website and its subdomains. We also use this information for analytics.

### Learn about digitalization with our newsletter

We’ll send how-to articles, case studies, and Yalantis updates to your inbox every Thursday!
